CONTACT



+32.487.92.97.47



rhita.lamdouar@proximus.com



Brussels, Belgium



www.linkedin.com/in/rhita-lamdouar



https://github.com/rhita1403

SKILLS

Soft skills

Bridge builder Oral & written communication Adaptability

Hard skills

Programming (Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Python, R, Sql, Figma, Github, Heroku) Web development (HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Vue.js) Microsoft Office 365

Languages

French (C2) English (C1)
Dutch (B2) Spanish (B2)
German (A1) Arabic (A2)

AWARDS

Proximus & Molengeek Hackathon May 2022 Winner in Fiber category - Data Science project

International Business Mgt Grant May 2019

Université Laval, Québec -Business game assistant

BCG Strategy Cup February 2019 **Finalist - Mastercard**

PROJECTS

Izevent - Event planner web app for organizing easily small events

Kitchme - Airbnb type platform to rent kitchens

Rhita Lamdouar

Web developer

PROFILE INFO

Having successfully concluded my two-year management traineeship at Proximus, I embarked on a new journey: a two-month intensive coding program with Le Wagon. Combining my soft skills - such as active listening, bridge builder and rapid learning with my newfound expertise in programming and web development, I'm ready to help people transforming their vision of an ideal web app into a reality!

EXPERIENCE

Sept 2021 - Sept 2023

Management Trainee - Proximus

Analytics translator - 3rd assigment

Operational Implementation Manager - 2nd assigment

Service Transformation Hero - 1st assignment

August - September 2019

Web developer - Université Saint-Louis

Front End development for a business game platform

July 2019

Administrative Student Job - BNP Paribas

Administrative tasks in support teams

2016-2019

Tutor in mathematics and science - Schola ULB

Support to students in elementary and high schools in various topics such as mathematics and physics

EDUCATION

Oct 2023 - Dec 2023 Web development bootcamp

Le Wagon - Paris

Sept 2019 - June 2021 Master of Business Engineering

Solvay Brussels School - Brussels

Sept 2020 - Jan 2021 Exchange Program

Wirtschaftsuniversität - Vienna

Sept 2016 - June 2019 Bachelor of Business Engineering

University Saint-Louis - Brussels